[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal did Whoopi Goldberg voice in the 1994 animated movie The Lion King?", "correct_answer": "Hyena", "incorrect_answers": ["Hornbill", "Meerkat", "Lioness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Gustav Papendick bought the second bread-slicer.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This disorder, also known as manic depression, involves high risk of death through suicide.", "correct_answer": "Bipolar Disorder", "incorrect_answers": ["Dependent Personality Disorder", "Antisocial Personality Disorder", "Schizophrenia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the literal meaning of the word giraffe considering its Arabic origin?", "correct_answer": "Tall", "incorrect_answers": ["Unbelievable", "Ambiguous", "Scary"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie 48 Hrs., Ganz escapes from prison with the help of his friend Billy Bear. Where does he go after he escapes?", "correct_answer": "A hotel in the area", "incorrect_answers": ["San Francisco Giants game", "Chicago Cubs game", "Disneyland"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which country or state was the first to be attacked in WWII?", "correct_answer": "Poland", "incorrect_answers": ["Denmark", "Hawaii", "US Virgin Islands"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie Sleepless in Seattle runs 105 minutes. For how many minutes are the lead actor and lead  actress in the same scene?", "correct_answer": "2", "incorrect_answers": ["22", "44", "15"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ouzo is the preferred drink in this country. It is produced from pressed grapes, herbs and berries.", "correct_answer": "Greece", "incorrect_answers": ["Hungary", "Macedonia", "Turkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Brazil, Argentina, Chile, Paraguay, Uruguay, and Venezuela, where Italian cuisine is especially popular, there is a custom to eat this traditional Italian pasta on the 29th day of each month.", "correct_answer": "gnocchi", "incorrect_answers": ["stelline", "agnolotti", "pastina"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of Johann Strauss Is sons became known as The Waltz King and was instrumental in popularizing the waltz in Vienna during the 19th century?", "correct_answer": "Johan Strauss II", "incorrect_answers": ["Josef Strauss", "Eduard Strauss", "Ferdinand Strauss"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What villain did Michael Keaton face in his first Batman movie?", "correct_answer": "The Joker", "incorrect_answers": ["Catwoman", "The Penguin", "The Riddler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does Luke Skywalker go to look at after Han Solo tells him he is heading back to the base?", "correct_answer": "Meteorite", "incorrect_answers": ["The Probe Droid", "Stormtroopers", "At-At Walker"]}]